特瑞,我,我知道我在这里干的时间并不长
Terry,I know I haven't worked here very long but would it be possible...
但我在想您是否能考虑预支给我100块薪水
...if I got a $1 00 advance on my salary?
预支?
An advance?
这样我才能和家里人共度感恩节
So I can spend Thanksgiving with my family.
每年,我们全家都去韦尔滑雪 通常都是我父亲为我出票钱
Every year we ski in Vail,and my father pays for my ticket.
但是我现在已经开始学习独立
But I've started this independent thing...
嗯,这实际上也是我为什么要干这份…“工作”
...which is actually why I took this "job. "
瑞秋,瑞秋,亲爱的
Rachel,Rachel,sweetheart!
你是一位非常,非常糟糕的女招待
You' re a terrible,terrible waitress.
真的,真的糟糕透顶
Really,really awful.
好吧,我,我明白你的意思了 我同意您说的
I hear what you're saying. I'm with you.
但是我,我一直很努力地在做
But I'm trying really hard,and I think I'm doing better.
我想我会做得更好的
I really do.
-有人需要咖啡吗? -是的,这里
-Does anybody need coffee? -Yeah,over here.
噢,你看!
Look at that.
六人行 第1季 第09集 超狗气球飞了
The One Where Underdog Gets Away
打扰一下,先生. 您是这里的老主顾了
Excuse me,sir? Hi. You come in here all the time.
不知道您是否能考虑预支一点小费给我?
Do you think there's a possibility that you could advance me my tips?
算我没说. 我为以前用咖啡泼到您表示歉意
Okay,okay. That's fine. Fine. Sorry about that spill before!
还差98块5
Only 98.50 to go!
你知道老爸老妈要去波多黎各过感恩节吗?
Did you know Mom and Dad are going to Puerto Rico for Thanksgiving?
-不,他们不会 -他们要去.布莱明斯邀请了他们
-What? No,they're not. -Yes,the Blymans invited them.
你乱讲
You' re wrong.
-我没有乱讲 -你就是在乱讲
-I am not wrong. -You' re wrong.
我刚和他们通过电话
No,I just talked to them.
我要打电话给妈妈
I' m calling Mom.
-嘿,嘿 -嘿
-Hey,hey. -Hey!
这里是“紧急求助部”,你化了妆吗?
And this from the Cry for Help Department: Are you wearing makeup?
是的.从今天起,我的正式身份就是 乔伊.崔比安尼,演员兼模特
Yes,I am. As of today,I'm officially Joey T ribbiani,actor/model.
真有趣,因为我正想说: 你看起来更像,乔伊.崔比安尼,男人兼女人
That's funny. I was thinking you look more like,Joey T ribbiani,man/woman.
-你给什么当模特? -你知道那些城市免费门诊的招贴画吗?
-What were you modeling for? -Posters for the free clinic.
哇,那你不就成了那些 “健康一族”中的一员了吗?
So you' re gonna be one of those healthy guys?
-那个哮喘病人还真可爱 -你知道你为什么代言吗?
-The asthma guy's really cute. -Know which one you'll be?
不知道,但是我听说脑膜炎还缺人,所以…
No,but I hear Lyme disease is open,so you know....
-祝你好运,老兄.我希望你能染上 -谢谢
-Good luck,man. I hope you get it. -Thanks.
好吧,你是对的 他们怎能抛下我们不管? 这可是感恩节
You were right. How can they do this? It's Thanksgiving!
我在我那儿做顿大餐,怎么样? 我会做得和妈妈的味一样的
What if I cook dinner at my place? I'll make it just like Mom's.
你会弄成块的土豆泥给我吃吗?
Will you make mashed potatoes with the lumps?
这个,他们真不该把土豆… 我做土豆块
They're not actually supposed to I'll work on the lumps.
-乔伊,你要回家,是吗? -没错
-Joey,you' re going home? -Yeah.
钱德,你还在抵制所有清教徒的节日吗?
Chandler,you' re still boycotting all the pilgrim holidays?
-当然,他们中的任何一个 -菲比,你要和你外婆一起过?
-Every single one of them. -Phoebe,you'll be with your grandma?
是的,还有她的男朋友
And her boyfriend.
但我们是在12月庆祝,因为他过阴历节日
We're celebrating Thanksgiving in December because he's lunar.
那么,你星期四有空了?
So you're free Thursday then?
-是的.噢,我能来吗? -当然
-Yeah. Oh,can I come? -Yeah.
-瑞秋,你定下来要去韦尔吗? -没错.“咻,咻,咻!”
-Rach,are you gonna make it to Vail? -Absolutely. Shoop,shoop,shoop.
-还差102元就可成行 -我记得刚才是差98块5
-Only $1 02 to go. -I thought it was 98. 50?
没错,但我又摔了一个杯子
Yeah,well,it was,but l I broke a cup,so....
-我到卡萝那里去 -噢噢! 我们干嘛不叫上她?
-Well,l' m off to Carol's. -Ooh,ooh,why don't we invite her?
噢噢，因为她是我的前妻,而且她可能还想带上她的
Ooh,ooh,because she's my ex-wife and will want to bring her...
噢噢，女同伴侣!
...ooh,ooh,lesbian life partner.
卡萝在吗?
Hi. Is Carol here?
-她开教工会去了 -噢,我过来想把我的头骨拿走
-No,she's at a faculty meeting. -I just came by to pick up my skull.
嗯,不是我的,是…
Well,not mine,but....
-进来! -谢谢
-Come in. -Thanks.
是这样,卡萝上回借走上课用的 我现在得拿回去还给博物馆
Carol borrowed it,and I have to get it back to the museum.
-它是什么样子? -就像一张没有皮的大脸
-What's it look like? -Kind of like a big face without skin.
是的,我对这个解释比较熟悉
Yes. I'm familiar with the concept.
-我们来找找看. -好吧
-We can just look for it. -Okay.
哇,你们有这么多关于怎样成为一名女同志的书
Wow,you guys sure have a lot of books about being a lesbian.
嗯,你知道吗,你必须接受一门课程
Well,you know,you have to take a course.
否则,他们不让你当同性恋
Otherwise they don't let you do it.
嘿,《乌龟耶尔特》.经典作品
Hey,Yertle the Turtle! A classic.
没错,我现在在念给宝宝听
Actually,I'm reading it to the baby.
噢,那个还没出生的宝宝?
The baby that hasn't been born yet?
你是不是疯了?
Wouldn't that mean you're crazy?
什么,你觉得宝宝在里面听不到声音?
You don't think they can hear sounds in there?
你不是开玩笑吧,我的意思是… 真的 你…真的跟宝宝说话吗?
You' re not serious? I mean,you really talk to it?
当然,经常说.我要让宝宝记住我的声音
Yeah,all the time. I want the baby to know my voice.
那,你提到过我吗?
Well,that's just Do you talk about me?
-有的,经常. -真的?
-Yeah. All the time. -Really?
但是,嗯,我们称你为提供精液的鲍鲍
But,we just refer to you as " Bobo the Sperm Guy. "
不行,如果她和宝宝说话 那我也应该有一些“肚子谈话时间”
If she's talking to it,I just think I should get some belly time too.
但这不表示我相信这个
Not that I believe this.
噢,我相信.我觉得宝宝什么都能听见
I believe it. I think the baby can hear everything.
-真的? -我可以演示给你看.可能会有点怪异
-Really? -I'll show you. This'll seem weird.
你得把你的头放在这只火鸡里面
But you put your head inside this turkey...
然后大伙儿说话,你肯定能听到我们说的
...and we'll all talk and you'll hear everything we say.
我想说我完全赞成这个实验
I'd just like to say I'm totally behind this experiment.
而且,我还非常想把你的脑袋涂上黄油
In fact,I'd very much like to butter your head.
-嘿 -瑞秋,钱拿到没有?
-Hey. -Rach,did you make your money?
没有,都关门了 忘掉韦尔吧,忘掉家庭团聚吧
No,not even close. Forget Vail. Forget seeing my family.
忘掉“咻,咻,咻.”吧
Forget shoop,shoop,shoop.
瑞秋,你的信 -谢谢,放在桌上就行了
-Rach,here's your mail. -Thanks. You can put it on the table.
不,这是你的信!
No. Here's your mail!
谢谢,你把它放在桌子上就行了
Thanks. You can put it on the table!
你不想现在就打开它吗?
Would you just open it!
喔,天哪!你们真好!
Oh,my God! You guys are great!
大伙凑的
We all chipped in.
-大伙? -你欠我20块
-We did? -You owe me $20.
谢谢!太感谢了!
Thank you. Thank you so much!
钱德,这是你的感恩节大餐 你的西红柿汤
Chandler,got your traditional holiday feast. T omato soup...
你的奶酪杂拌和你的特大号洋葱小吃
...grilled-cheese fixings and a family-size bag of Funyuns.
等等,钱德,这是你的感恩节晚餐吗? 你和这个节日到底有什么过节?
This is your Thanksgiving dinner? What is it with you and this holiday?
-好吧,我9岁那年… -噢,我厌恶这个故事
-I'm 9 years old. -I hate this story!
我们全家刚刚吃完一顿丰盛的感恩节大餐.我…
We've finished this magnificent Thanksgiving dinner. I have...
…塞了满嘴的南瓜派
...a mouthful of pumpkin pie.
我的父母就选择那会儿来告诉我: 他们要离婚了
And then my parents tell me they're getting divorced.
噢,天啊!
Oh,my God!
是的.一旦你有过这样的负面印像 就很难对感恩节大餐有兴趣了
Very difficult to enjoy Thanksgiving dinner once you've seen it in reverse.
这是什么? 我从没在妈妈的感恩节大餐中看到这个
What's this? I never saw this at Mom's.
-这是红薯 -拜托….
-It's a yam. -Hello....
这不是红薯.红薯都是放在紫色罐头里的
This isn't a yam. Yam comes in purple cans.
不是的,红薯不是放在这里的
They don't They don't come in these.
罗斯,不要指责什么错误, 滚开
Ross,don't take this the wrong way or anything,but back off.
-我们一起工作过 -有吗?
-We used to work together. -We did?
是的,在梅西百货 你是那个“迷幻”女郎,对吧?
Yeah,at Macy's. You' re the Obsession girl,right?
-是的 -我是“阿拉米香水”男
-Yes. -I was the Aramis guy.
-阿拉米?阿拉米? -哦,想起来了
-Aramis. Aramis. Aramis. -Yeah,right!
-我得说,你是那里面最棒的 -少来了!
-You' re the best in the business. -Get out.
你太让人吃惊了 你知道什么时候喷雾，什么时候放回原处
You' re amazing! You know when to spritz. You know when to lay back.
真的吗? 我受宠若惊了
Really? You don't know what that means to me.
你今晚闻起来妙极了. 你身上是什么?
You smell great tonight. What are you wearing?
什么也没有!
Nothing.
-你想不想去喝上一杯? -好的,哦
-Listen,do you wanna go get a drink? -Yeah,that would be
-怎么了? -我刚想起,我还有要紧的事要做
-What's wrong? -I have to do something.
噢,什么事情?
What?
-离开 -等等,嘿,等等!
-Leave. -Wait,wait,wait!
“马里奥没有告诉你：性病-你永远无从知道谁会染上它”
我想你们都看见了
So I guess you all saw it.
-什么? -看见什么?
-What? -Saw what?
不,我们只是在笑.你知道,笑也是会“传染”的
No,we' re just laughing. You know how laughter can be infectious.
我得另找个地方过感恩节了 我全家都认为我有性病
Set another place for Thanksgiving. My entire family thinks I have VD.
今夜,此花怒放
"Tonight,on a very special Blossom. "
嗯,看起来不错.好了
Looking good! Okay!
苹果酒搞定,火鸡搞定,红薯搞定
Cider's mulling,turkey's turkeying,yams are yamming....
怎么了?
What?
我不知道.妈妈不在厨房感觉就是不一样
I don't know. It's just not the same without Mom in the kitchen.
够了!出去别烦我!
Get out and stop annoying me!
这样有点像了
Oh,that's closer.
我拿到票了! 我拿到票了!
I got the tickets!
再过5个小时我就要 “咻,咻,咻.”
Five hours from now,shoop,shoop,shoop!
-噢,别“咻”了,好吗? -我去收拾行李
-Oh,you must stop shooping. -Okay,l' m gonna get my stuff.
钱德,你今晚会来吗?
Will you come in?
不,我喜欢和欢乐保持安全距离!
I prefer to keep a safe distance from all this merriment.
注意,南瓜派来了!
Look out! Incoming pumpkin pie!
你在塞填料的时候我们是笑了,但其实根本不好笑
We laughed when you did it with the stuffing,but that's not funny.
喂,莫妮卡,我有一个问题 我没看见有塔特酒
Hey,Monica,I got a question. I don't see any T ator Tots.
-这不叫问题! -但是我的妈妈总是做的.这是传统
-That's not a question. -My mom makes them. It's a tradition.
弄点火鸡肉在叉子上,配上点蓝莓,还有塔特酒!
You get a piece of turkey on your fork,a little cranberry sauce and a Tot!
因为我的“病”,我不能与家人团聚了,真糟糕透了
I mean,it's bad enough I can't be with my family because of my disease.
好吧,好吧
All right. Fine.
今晚的土豆泥会有成块的和有酒味的
Tonight's potatoes will be mashed,with lumps and in the form of Tots.
我要去和还没出生的宝宝说话了
All right,I'm off to talk to my unborn child.
妈妈从不打我
Okay,Mom never hit.
搞定了
Okay,all done.
干吗,菲比,你在搅烂土豆吗?罗斯要吃块状的!
Phoebe,did you whip the pota? Ross needs lumps!
噢,很抱歉
Oh,l' m sorry! I just
噢,我以为搅烂了以后,可以加一些豌豆和洋葱
I thought we could have them whipped and then add some peas and onions.
为什么我们要那样做?
Why do that?
嗯,因为我妈都是那样做的,你知道,在她去世之前
Because then they'd be just like my mom used to make it,before she died.
好吧,第3种吃法出现
Okay. Three kinds of potatoes coming up.
大伙,再见. 感谢你们
Okay. Goodbye,you guys! Thanks for everything!
噢,天呐! 噢,抱歉!
Oh,God,look at Sorry! I'm so sorry.
最不可思议事情发生了! 超狗刚刚飞了!
An unbelievable thing happened! Underdog got away!
-那个气球吗? -不,是真的卡通人物
-The balloon? -No,no,the actual cartoon character.
当然是那个气球!
Of course the balloon!
梅西百货前他断线了 后来在华盛顿广场公园上又被发现了
He broke free and was spotted flying over Washington Square Park.
-我要上屋顶去看,谁要去? -我不去了
-I'm going to the roof. Who's with me? -I can't!
来吧.80英尺长的充气狗在城市上空游荡 发生的概率是多少
An 80-foot dog over the city? How often does that happen?
几乎不可能发生
Almost never.
-拿上钥匙了吗… -好的
-Got the keys? -Okay.
只要你准备好了随时可以开始
Anytime you' re ready.
好的,好的,开始
Okay. Okay,here we go.
这里吗,我得对着哪里说?
Okay. Where am I talking to here?
我的意思是， 好像只有一个地方能让他听见,但是 …
There is one way that offers a certain acoustical advantage,but....
对着鼓出来的地方就可以
Just aim for the bump.
好的,开始了
Okay. Okay. Okay,here goes.
你知道,我,你知道,我做不出来
You know,I can't do this. This is
噢,这太奇怪了.我感到自己像个傻瓜
It's too weird. I feel stupid.
那你就别说了 你不必因为苏珊做了你就非得做
It's fine. You don't have to do it just because Susan does it.
你好吗?宝宝!你好,你好
Hello,baby. Hello. Hello.
我们第一次见大狗飘在公园上空
the moment we first saw the dog shadow fall over the park!
是的,但是他们必须把他射下来吗? 太残忍了
But did they have to shoot him down? That was just mean.
现在火鸡应该是外焦…
Right now the turkey should be crispy on the outside...
…而且里嫩了
...and juicy on the inside.
还站在这里干嘛?
Why are we standing here?
-等你开门.你拿着钥匙
We're waiting for you to open the door. You have the keys.
我没有
No,I don't.
你拿了.出来的时候,你说拿上钥匙了
Yes,you do. When we left,you said,"Got the keys. "
我没有.我问:“拿上钥匙了吗”?
No,I didn't. I asked,"Got the keys? "
不、不、不.你是说:“拿上钥匙了”
No,no,no. You said,"Got the keys! "
你们俩都没拿钥匙?
Do either of you have the keys?
-烤炉还开着 -噢,我得拿我的票!
-The oven is on! -I've gotta get my ticket!
-等等,我们有一把你家的备用钥匙 -快去拿,快去!
-Wait! We have a copy of your key. -Get it!
你这种语气无法加快我的速度
That tone won't make me go any faster.
-乔伊！ -这还凑合
-Joey. -That one will.
每个人都对我说:你得选个专业
And everyone's telling me,"You gotta pick a major. "
于是我鼓起勇气挑了古生物学
So on a dare,I picked paleontology.
可能你不懂我正说什么 因为事实上,你还是一个胎儿
And you have no idea what I'm saying,because,face it,you' re a fetus.
你应该高兴因为你不会再有鳃
You're happy you don't have gills anymore.
你不用老是说话,你也可以对他唱歌
You don't have to talk to it. You can sing
噢.拜托,我才不想对着你的肚子唱歌!
Please. I am not singing to your stomach,okay?
进展如何?
How's it going?
嘘! 我们来了
Here we come
沿着那些街道走着
Walking down the street
每个人的表情都很可笑
Get the funniest looks from Everyone we meet
嘿,嘿!
Hey,hey
-喂,噢,你觉到了吗? -是的,我有
-Hey,did you just feel that? -I did.
-他总这样吗? -不,没有,这是第一次
-Does it always? -That was the first.
接着唱!接着唱!
IKeep singing! IKeep singing!
嘿,嘿,你是我的宝宝,我已经等不及想见你
Hey,hey,you 're my baby And I can 't wait to meet you
等你出来后,我会为你买百吉饼 然后带你去动物园
When you come out I'll buy you a bagel Then we 'll go to the zoo
-又来了一次! -这次我也感觉到了!
-lt did it again! -I felt it that time!
“嘿,嘿,我是你的爸爸.没有乳房的那个…”
Hey,hey,I'm your daddy I'm the one without any breasts
真是太棒了.现在已经五点了 我的飞机已经从登机口拖走了
This is great. It's 5:00. My plane is pulling away from the gate.
-也许你可以搭晚班飞机 -没有了
-Maybe you can take a later flight. -There is none.
-你可以明天去 -明天就不是感恩节了!
-You can go tomorrow. -T omorrow is not Thanksgiving!
我想让你开心一点,你却总是中间打断我
If l' m gonna cheer you up,you have to meet me halfway.
你能快一点吗?
Can you go any faster?
锁眼只有一个,而钥匙有上千把 你算算看
I got one keyhole and a zillion keys! You do the math.
你怎么会有那么多钥匙?
Why do you guys have so many keys in there anyway?
紧急情况,就像现在这样
For an emergency just like this.
你听着,假笑的家伙
All right. Listen,smirky!
要不是你和你那愚蠢的气球,现在我就在飞机上…
If not for your stupid balloon,I'd be on a plane...
…看着一个女人这样做了 但现在我却不能!
...watching a woman do this... right now. But l' m not!
你说你带了钥匙,我发誓
You said you had the keys!
不,没有.我如果拿了钥匙,我会说“拿了” 显然我没拿那该死的钥匙
No,I didn't! I wouldn't say I had the keys unless I had the keys!
够了,别再提钥匙了
That's it! Enough with the keys. No one say keys!
为什么我应该拿钥匙?
Why would I have the keys?!
-不考虑你说你拿了的事实? -但是我没拿
-Aside from the fact you said you did? -I didn't!
-嗯,你应该拿 -为什么?
-You should've. -Why?
-因为! -为什么?
-Because! -Why?
一切都该是我的责任吗?难道我为大家准备晚餐还不够吗?
Everything's my responsibility? Isn't it enough that l' m making dinner?
每个人要的土豆泥都不一样 我得做各种样式的土豆泥
Everyone wants a different kind of potato,so I'm making them.
有谁关心过我要哪种土豆泥吗?
Does anybody care what kind of potatoes I want? No!
没有,没有…
No! No!
菲比要有洋葱和豌豆的土豆泥 “马里奥”要有塔特酒口味的
Just as long as Phoebe gets her peas and onions,and Mario gets his T ots
这是我第一次搞感恩节大餐
It's my first Thanksgiving,and l
现在全焦了,…我…
It's all burnt,and I can't....
莫妮卡,只有狗现在能听见你说的 好了,门已经开.进去吧
Monica,only dogs can hear you now. Look,the door's open. Here we go.
-好吧,钱德,别把钥匙丢了. -不
-All right,Chandler,don't lose this. -No
嗯,火鸡烧焦了
Well,the turkey's burnt!
这种土豆完了,这种土豆完了,这种土豆也完了
Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes are ruined!
“我们沿着…”?
Here we come
走下去
Walking down the
妈妈的厨房可不是这个味
This doesn't smell like Mom's.
不像是吧? 你不是要土豆块吗 罗斯? 好,拿去,伙计.这里有一个!
It doesn't,does it? You wanted lumps? Here you go,buddy. You got one!
-不要对我吼.是你把晚饭烧着了 -嗨,不要让她再发飙啦!
-Don't yell at me. You burned dinner! -Hey,don't make her squeak again!
噢,天哪,飞机已经飞走了 看来我只能留下来和你们在一起了
God,this is great! The plane is gone. I guess I'm stuck here with you guys.
我们本来都有个不错的计划的 这不是大伙的第一选择
We all had better plans. This was nobody's first choice!
噢,真的吗? 那我何苦要做这顿丰盛的感恩节大餐?
Oh,really? So why was I busting my ass to make this delicious dinner?
-你管这叫丰盛吗? -给我安静!
-You call that delicious? -You be quiet!
闭嘴,闭嘴,闭嘴!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
终于有了点感恩节的气氛了
Now this feels like Thanksgiving.
滑雪
Skiing.
咻,咻,咻….
Shoop,shoop,shoop....
咻
Shoop.
-噢! -什么?
-Eww. -What?
丑陋裸男正从烤炉中取出他的火鸡
Ugly Naked Guy's taking his turkey out of the oven.
-谁在乎啊? -他刚刚坐到肉汤里了
-Who cares? -He just sat in gravy.
噢,我的天.丑陋裸男不是一个人
Oh,my God! He's not alone.
他正和一个丑陋裸女共进感恩节晚餐
Ugly Naked Guy is having Thanksgiving dinner with Ugly Naked Gal.
我得看看
I gotta see this!
丑陋裸男真爽!
All right,Ugly Naked Guy!
裸舞开场了!
Ugly naked dancing!
有人陪真好
It's nice that he has someone.
可以切了吗?
Shall I carve?
-怎样都行 -好
-By all means. -All right.
谁想要浅色起司,谁想要深色起司?
Who wants light cheese,and who wants dark cheese?
我一点也不想知道深色起司是怎么来的
I don't even want to know about the dark cheese.
-有人想要和我分这块吗? -噢,我要
-Does anybody wanna split this? -I will.
你们必须先许个愿望. -许愿?
-You guys have to make a wish. -Make a wish?
来吧,这是感恩节(代替许愿骨许愿的感恩节传统)
Come on,you know,Thanksgiving.
噢!你得到大半了.你许的什么愿?
You got the bigger half! What did you wish for?
得到大半
The bigger half.
我敬各位一杯
All right,I'd like to propose a toast.
来一杯
A little toast here. Ding,ding!
我知道这不是你们本来计划的感恩节
This isn't the Thanksgiving you planned...
但是对我来说,这样也挺棒的
...but for me,this has been really great.
我想,这是因为它没和离婚或者呕吐搭界
I think because it didn't involve divorce or projectile vomiting.
如果你去了韦尔,如果你和你家人在一起
If you'd gone to Vail or if you had been with your family...
你没有……“梅毒”那些玩意
...or if you didn't have syphilis and stuff...
我们就不能一起过
...we wouldn't be together.
所以我想说的就是:
I guess what l' m trying to say is that...
谢天谢地你们的感恩节计划都砸了
... I' m very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
-真是感人! -谢谢
-That's so sweet! -Thank you.
-祝你有个糟糕的圣诞节. -还有一个失败的新年
-Here's to a lousy Christmas! -And a crappy New Year!
-没错! -没错!
-Hear,hear! -Hear,hear!
小便失禁!
停止家庭暴力 !
有痔疮吗?
三次“东尼奖”获得者